Neha Madhogaria

•Address: R. No. 105, H. No. R82, R Block, Uppal Southend, Sector 49, Sohna Rd, Near DAV Public School, Gurugram- 122018 • Phone: +91 98303 66721 • E- Mail: nehamarketingsol@gmail.com •D.O.B: 30.05.1986 • Skype: neha.madhogaria • Website: marketingsol.in

Personal Profile

Marketing professional with 7+ years of knowledge in integrated marketing communications for various organizations and clients. Driven and results- oriented; possess excellent interpersonal skills; combined with solid brand management and creative background. Highly adaptable and personable individual, with a global perspective and exceptionally acute multicultural understanding.

Experience

Freelance Marketing Consultant to Multiple Organizations (2011- Till Date): India

- Consulting as a Freelancer to Cofinex Inc. Ltd., Ideal Insurance Brokers Pvt. Ltd., Easy Elite English Educational Trust, Karma Kettle Tea, ISKCON- GEV Resort, InnerCircle Advertising (I) Pvt. Ltd. for various brands, Ogilvy & Mather (Intern) for Vodafone brand. My profile includes:
- Assisting in all PR and media management, influencer engagement, market research, product launch, branding, blogging, photoshoot, events and customer interactions
- Responding to all gueries on official company phone and emails
- Supplying quotes to Indiamart leads, Amazon, E Bay etc.
- Following up with prospective clients after initial meetings explaining product line
- Brainstorming, creating new ideas and liaising with client servicing, studio team to proof read and release artworks, digital agency, sales coordinator for online promotions and advertising strategy
- Analyzing client brief to prepare proposals, maintaining client order inventory spreadsheet with updated contact details of every client
- Follow up with accounts to ensure timely payment collection from clients
- Designing marketing collaterals and digital marketing activities

Amrfeo Pte. Ltd. (01/07/2018-29/02/2020): Kolkata

- As a Senior Manager- Marketing & Sales, devised and implemented sales, marketing and media plans adhering to established targets for all manufactured goods such as bentonite, polymer, foam for civil engineering applications
- Managed the development of new product namely super absorbent with usage in various fields ranging from pharmaceutical to agriculture
- Collated and interpreted data on the effectiveness of marketing strategies
- Monitored marketing trends and competitors, and effectively responded to the results
- Oversaw and optimized digital marketing efforts using social media, email and website
- International markets, had to be worked on in close co- ordination with the Director according to internal regulations

Bengal Aerotropolis Projects Limited (01/04/2016–29/05/2017): Kolkata

- Employed as Brand & Marcom Executive, my profession consisted of:
- Managing marketing, branding strategy for Sujalaam- The Skycity at Durgapur.
 Developed, conducted and implemented all online, offline marketing communication initiatives, media measures, press releases, brand awareness and corporate identity to increase sales
- Managed and executed tactical promotions and offers to drive incremental revenue
- Handled company website and social media channels by engaging followers from different groups on facebook, twitter, linkedin, blogs and youtube
- Created social media calendar, social media reports per month/ week
- Directed digital strategy (including SEO, ORM, Wiki page etc.) to develop web marketing as an integral part of overall marketing strategy
- Identify sales requirements, generate sales enquiries and make presentations

 Fixing up appointments to meet with various organizations, commerce associations and show details of the project to achieve results

Ruchi Realty Holdings Limited (31/12/2013-31/03/2016): Kolkata

- Served as an **Assistant Manager- Marketing** in this real estate company
- Planned, implemented, monitored and evaluated communications strategy for advertisements, promotions, graphics and collateral to support marketing objectives targeting maximization of the business's positive exposure in local, national and international markets
- Managed digital campaigns and online portals such as 99 Acres, Magicbricks, Commonfloor, SEO, SEM, SMS blast, website, social media, emailers, newsletters etc.
- Monitored the effectiveness of campaigns, managing relevant social media accounts and the target audience
- Provide assistance in ERP, generating money receipts & demand, allotment letters
- Enquiry generation from new customers/ assigned segments through online marketing, ATL & BTL activities
- Play a key role during local exhibitions and events by providing the corporate branding communication material in the form of posters, flyers, brochures etc.
- Improved marketing strategy with new advertising (radio, print, hoardings, direct marketing and online) to increase brand awareness
- C.E.S.C. related applications. Preparing M.O.M, various marketing & enquiry reports, drafting letters, bills, press estimates, brand capital list, maintaining all database etc.

Education

Dec. 2019 WebTek Labs Pvt. Ltd., India

Master Program of Digital Marketing

Certifications: Google & HubSpot, WebTek Labs (Google Partners)

Nov. 2010 Aston University, UK

Master of Science, Marketing Management

Research dissertation topic: Integrated Model of Growth Strategies for Small Firms in Developing Economies

June 2009 University of Manchester, UK

Bachelor of Science (Hons), Management

June 2006 Royal Holloway College- University of London, UK

University Foundation Programme (Equivalent to "A" Levels)

Achievements & Skills

Achievements- Peer Mentor at University of Manchester (2007-2009), Awarded Distinction in UFP, under University of London (2006), Successfully completed Finishing School Course from J. D. Birla College- Kolkata (2004).

Computers– Graphic & Web Design, SEO, Web Analytics & GTM, PPC or SEM, SMO, SMM, Email, Inbound and Affiliate Marketing, Adsense & Blogging, ERP- Far Vision (marketing modules), MS Office.

Languages- English, Hindi, Bengali & Spanish (basics).

Personal Qualities- Organized, Creative, Detail Oriented, Presentation.

Interests

Sports- Swimming, Exercising, Badminton and Yoga.

Travel- Europe, US, Australia, New Zealand, UK, U.A.E and Asia.

Others- Reading, Travelling, Calligraphy, Art, Spirituality and Driving.